most topics feel like I probably already
covered this this was a weird noise in
my apartment and I've no idea where it's
coming from
nobody can tell direction of sound so I
just kind of have to deal with this idea
of internal versus external validation
that I realize that you know I don't
think anyone else would think that I
have that I care that much about what
people think of me but realize and I
didn't think I did either but realizing
all the ways that I do did in fact and
also just looking to society for
validation on does this look okay on me
is this the right color is this the
right fit is this the right size and
realizing oh there's like some truth
there especially if you're in like a
business meeting or something you want
to look a certain way and present a
certain when it's more important to
present a certain persona for the
mission you're doing than to be your
authentic self then you know do the
mission but otherwise be your authentic
self and realizing today I went to go
shop for glasses
I hate glasses shopping because it's
something that triggers me a little bit
from being a child and having to wear
glasses that were the cheapest and
listener time period where glasses
weren't considered cool now people wear
them without median to do the big things
glasses and freckles people are also
putting freckles on their face and
although I love my freckles now didn't
even love my glasses was one of the
reasons I haven't gotten surgery but
finding ones that I'm okay with that
looked good on my face but also it's
more about internally like what do I
think looks good so I didn't bring a
friend this time because I was like
although I don't necessarily trust my
own opinion I am in that realm to make
myself look good in society I care more
about my internal validation so what
makes what do I like what do I feel good
good and I tried on lots of the men's
pairs of glasses I didn't like them I
didn't go in for the women's ones but
finding
all of the ways that I do that did I
and the flipside of that too is of
course pushing things away like wanting
to look like a scrub which I do a lot is
just the flipside of needing to look
really good for everyone and it's just
as unhealthy so being like okay what
makes me feel attractive what makes me
feel powerful what makes me feel like my
authentic self and every step I move
forward is awesome like I mean I love my
new haircut in a way that I've never
loved a haircut before and and it feels
like it's me that it's it's something
that like oh that's the one I was
looking for it's a strange feeling and
it's all about it's all about me it's
not about tracking a partner it's not
about getting a job or putting out a
certain persona it's just about what is
my most authentic self and it's been an
it's a fun journey and I don't think I'm
ever going to necessarily be done it by
the time I'm done I'll probably have a
new haircut that I like absolutely match
everything to that now I'm in the mood
to kind of start clothes shopping and
things that means something to me but
all the things I like are available
online and when you get them they never
fit right we need an app for that and
Apple when I can we're sure I can be
like nope that rides up on me and I can
suggest things what I would like I said
my time doing creating apps in my head
that I've no idea how to actually
perfect for things that my intelligence
either does do but I need it to do more
like science and math I'm fairly good at
science and math but I can't do all the
compilations and algorithms needed to
like make decisions on the best products
to buy and the best for yeah I mean
millions of decisions we make in our
lifetime but also for the things that
I'm not so great at like relationships
and fashion and then again I don't want
someone to dress me like for society but
to be like hey here's my style here's my
wardrobe what should I wear to this
event what should i what should I wear
that I don't like it when my clothes do
this right like I know for me I sweat
and so if something's like in my armpits
then it just gets gross and looks like
it's sweaty and the more I like stress
about
course than what happens so the more
it's like okay like it it's a positive
feedback loop it feels very negative and
so finding clothes like it's all by
something that I love and then I'll
never wear it because the first time I
wear it again it looks gross and so I
know then I know that happens and then I
feel self-conscious and then I just
never wear it even though I loved it
it's why I bought it and more rambling
every day is rambling
I've got to go still write for an hour
explain my global cooperative that
energizes me and it's my mission on this
planet you did my more authentic self
just like I should actually leave the
house and be with people sometimes
figuring those things out my hobbies are
what my interests are boom attract you
yeah it's funny the more I narrow it
down who I'm attracted to the more
people attracted to that doesn't make
sense does it it was like everyone
anyone will do well and then make them
more I'm like no the specific group then
I'll find people aren't even necessarily
part of that specific group that I have
more crushes on and I ever had before so
it's nice I like crushing having crushes
on people it's a nice feeling I don't
know when I'll be brave enough to
actually do anything about it but
currently enjoying that so remember
today's video is about this is day 27